Back when I was in Manchuria,
当年在满洲里的时候
knew a Japanese military officer,
认识一位日本军官，
Namanya Takeshi Yamashita.
山下武士那曼也。
Naoki Naeda who saved me.
救了我的苗田直树。
I've prepared everything
我已准备好一切
when will we go?
我们什么时候去？
Don't panic yet.
先别惊慌。
There's one thing
有一点
what I want to tell you.
我想告诉你什么。
Tuan Jiang.
Tuan Jiang.
Come on, let me introduce you.
来吧，让我给你介绍一下。
This is my friend.
这是我的朋友。
Ding Qiuyang.
Ding Qiuyang.
Miss Han Lu, how are you.
韩露小姐，你好吗？
Two!
二！
I've heard your name for a long time.
我听你的名字很久了。
Film Nona Han Lu.
电影《诺娜韩露》。
I've seen a lot.
我见过很多。
Now meet the real person
现在遇见真人了
those films
那些电影
filmed you so badly
把你拍得很糟糕
dear
亲爱的
Thank You.
谢谢。
He is also a director.
他也是一名导演。
Hope there is a chance to work with Miss Han Lu.
希望有机会和韩露小姐合作。
I still have friends.
我还有朋友。
So I won't bother you anymore.
所以我不会再打扰你了。
Good
好的
actually when are we going?
其实我们什么时候去？
Don't panic yet.
先别惊慌。
Come on, sit down first.
来吧，先坐下。
This time came to Shanghai,
这次来到上海，
things didn't go well.
事情进展不顺利。
I returned to Chongqing,
我回到了重庆，
it may be difficult to rest.
可能很难休息。
Now the country is in a difficult situation,
现在国家正处于困难时期，
Soldiers also make trouble.
军人也会制造麻烦。
And I,
和我，
also have a big responsibility.
也有很大的责任。
According to you,
照你说的，
how could I let you follow me
我怎么能让你跟着我
reach everywhere
到达各处
to the point of losing their place to live.
以至于失去居住的地方。
So
所以
This time I can't take you away
这次我不能带你走
So, same as before, right?
那么，和以前一样，对吗？
All swear
都发誓
just to make me happy for a moment.
只是为了让我高兴一会儿。
In the end, he will still leave me.
最终，他还是会离开我。
I want to be with you too.
我也想和你在一起。
Inseparable from you.
与你形影不离。
Live quietly and peacefully.
平静而平和地生活。
But hatred in the country
但国内却充满仇恨
I dare not hope
我不敢希望
marry me, okay?
嫁给我，好吗？
This time I'm really serious.
这次我是认真的。
Give me a little more time.
再给我一点时间。
I promise to you,
我答应你，
I will definitely come back to pick you up,
我一定会回来接你的
and marry you to be my bride.
并娶你为我的新娘。
Is it true?
这是真的吗？
Correct.
正确的。
Oh yes, today you are carrying out your duties,
哦，是的，今天你正在履行你的职责，
I went to the location.
我去了那个地点。
I am thinking
我在想
even though my gun had been taken
即使我的枪被拿走了
but
但
Can I come along to look around?
我可以一起去看看吗？
Guess who I met?
你猜我遇见了谁？
Who's that?
那是谁？
Left twin.
左边双胞胎。
I am thinking,
我在想，
how could he appear there
他怎么会出现在那里
she also talked to an old nun
她还和一位老修女交谈过
nun?
尼姑？
How can you be interested?
你怎么可能感兴趣？
I know you have a habit of collecting women's clothes
我知道你有收集女装的习惯
and there are still not enough nurse clothes
护士服还不够
go away
离开
My illness has changed a long time ago
我的病很久以前就已经改变了
I suddenly remembered
我突然想起
the person who saved Jiang Zhaoguo this afternoon
今天下午救了蒋兆国的人
seems to be a nurse
似乎是一名护士
Is that true?
真的吗？
So why don't you investigate?
那你为什么不调查一下呢？
Investigating what? I'll look into it
调查什么？我会调查一下
the nun covered her face
修女捂住脸
His face is not visible at all
根本看不到他的脸
and the place was a French concession
那地方是法租界
today it exploded and fired shots
今天它爆炸并开枪
we didn't have time to run
我们没有时间跑
Are you still checking on the nurse?
还在检查护士吗？
According to you
照你说的
what is a nurse?
什么是护士？
who disguised himself as Persik Kiri.
他伪装成 Persik Kiri。
As long as I'm not around,
只要我不在身边
ding Qiuyang will help me guard your life
丁秋阳帮我守护你的生命
Besides that,
除此之外，
he will also help you plan
他还会帮助你计划
your future career development.
您未来的职业发展。
Why have I never heard you tell it?
为什么我从来没有听你说过？
There are friends like this,
有这样的朋友，
he has also only been a director for two years.
他也只担任了两年的董事。
And also,
并且，
if there are spies who want to find trouble with you again,
如果再有间谍想找你的麻烦
you can ask for his help
你可以寻求他的帮助
isn't he the director?
他不是导演吗？
Correct.
正确的。
However, he...
然而，他...
There are quite a lot of roads.
有相当多的道路。
How will you go to Chongqing this time?
这次你准备怎样去重庆呢？
This is also a secret, right?
这也是一个秘密吧？
After arriving in Chongqing,
抵达重庆后，
will you call me?
你会给我打电话吗？
Of course.
当然。
Of course I will contact you.
我当然会联系你。
That's good then.
那就好了。
Although not next to him
虽然不在他身边
can often hear your cell phone number
经常能听到你的手机号码
enough already.
已经足够。
Then you
然后你
take care.
小心。
This time,
这次，
is it really real?
这是真的吗？
Of course.
当然。
I love you.
我爱你。
I love you too.
我也爱你。
Hurry up.
赶快。
I will kill you
我会杀了你
7th Brother, 7th Brother
七弟，七弟
What happened?
发生了什么？
Section Chief Chen
陈科长
he drinks too much
他喝太多了
took my knife and stabbed people.
拿了我的刀去刺人。
You killed this man?
你杀了这个人？
He is an anti-Japanese activist.
他是一位抗日活动家。
What proof do you have?
你有什么证据？
He passed our table
他经过我们的桌子
he said he scolded us were bastards
他说他骂我们是混蛋
isn't this proof?
这不是证据吗？
Just for scolding you
就是为了骂你
you kill people.
你杀人。
Scold me, I scold you Chairman Wang
骂我我骂你王主席
scolding the Japanese Empire!
骂日本帝国！
Did he deserve to die?
他该死吗？
Don't be emotional, don't be emotional.
不要情绪化，不要情绪化。
Don't be emotional.
不要情绪化。
Chief Chen, chief Chen
陈科长 陈科长
Chen's head
陈的头像
we are work friends
我们是工作朋友
dare to hit me.
竟然敢打我。
Don't be angry.
别生气。
Dare to hit me?
还敢打我？
Don't be emotional, don't be emotional.
不要情绪化，不要情绪化。
I took him away.
我把他带走了。
I brought him to his senses.
我让他清醒过来。
Road. - Let go.
路。- 松手。
Road.
路。
Two stabs, he hit me
两刀，他打到我了
7th brother
七弟
Who are you, bastard
你是谁啊混蛋
dare to hit me
敢打我
7th brother
七弟
Don't lose out on big things because of small things
不要因为小事而失去大事
I will kill him
我会杀他
enough already.
已经足够。
Two punctures.
两处刺伤。
Hit me, he...
打我吧，他……
Sis, that's it.
姐，就这样吧
Why do you think the same as him?
为什么你的想法和他一样？
Like this, like this.
像这样，像这样。
I'll pull it later
我稍后拉
How
如何
I choose Chen Jia Ping
我选陈家平
You don't think the same way as him
你的想法和他不一样
hit me!
打我！
Sis, don't be angry.
姐姐，别生气。
Here.
这里。
This.
这。
Wipe off sweat.
擦去汗水。
What's that?
那是什么？
Women's stuff
女士用品
haven't you changed it?
你没改过吗？
Why do you still steal women's things?
为什么还偷女人的东西？
I've changed it.
我已经改变了。
I used to steal women's underwear
我曾经偷过女人的内衣
now you see,
现在你看到了，
This fragrance is also an elegant item.
这款香水也是一款优雅的单品。
Am I making progress?
我有进步吗？
I'm telling you
我告诉你
I did not steal this item,
我没有偷这个物品，
I picked it up
我捡起它
which woman do you have?
你有哪个女人？
Twin left peach
左双桃
pick up where?
去哪里接？
Do you still remember some time ago?
你还记得不久前的事吗？
at that time, the fighters disguised themselves as the CCP
当时，战士们伪装成中共
to identify Chen Jiaping.
找出陈家平的身份。
Zhao An also hung it on the tree
赵安也把它挂在树上了
I picked it up at that time.
我当时就捡起来了。
Wait until I kill Chen Jia Ping
等我杀了陈家平
his woman will be yours
他的女人将是你的
I can't control that woman
我无法控制那个女人
I smelled the fragrance
我闻到了香味
I'm very satisfied.
我很满意。
Look, Yun Jin.
Look, Yun Jin.
Really didn't expect it
真的没想到
at the train station you can buy things as good as this
在火车站你可以买到这么好的东西
how do you know this was bought at the train station
你怎么知道这是在火车站买的
he said himself
他自己说
the day he first came to Shanghai,
刚来上海的那天，
when Zhao An interrogated him,
当赵安审问他时，
very fragrant.
很香。
Where do you get it?
你从哪里得到它？
From the train station.
从火车站出发。
Didn't he come from Wuhan to Shanghai?
他不是从武汉来上海的吗？
Correct.
正确的。
But this Yun Jin fragrance
但这云锦香
only in Nanjing,
仅在南京​​，
only sold at Nanjing Pukou Station.
仅南京浦口站有售。
So, what does it mean?
那么，这意味着什么呢？
This means that the Left Twin is lying.
这意味着左双胞胎在撒谎。
Do you know?
你知道吗？
Zhao An will be finished.
赵安就完了。
What's that?
那是什么？
According to me,
据我说，
zhao An will end!
赵安就完蛋了！
Zhao An, stop it!
赵安，住手！
What does that have to do with me?
这跟我有什么关系？
Do you think I don't know anything?
你以为我什么都不知道吗？
Komandan Luo.
Komandan Luo.
Gossip about the company,
关于公司的八卦，
just complete nonsense.
完全是胡说八道。
Don't believe it.
别相信。
I didn't ask you anything.
我什么也没问你。
You said there were rumors.
你说有谣言。
What's a rumor?
什么是谣言？
Say.
说。
Actually, what is a rumor?
其实，什么是谣言呢？
Zhao... Zhao An!
Zhao... Zhao An!
That bastard Zhao An forced me.
赵安那个混蛋逼我的。
The power is so great.
威力就是这么大。
How dare I fight back.
我怎么敢反击。
Komandan Luo.
Komandan Luo.
Please forgive me.
请原谅我。
Seeing that we have been married for a long time,
看着我们结婚这么久了，
I've done so many things for you,
我为你做了很多事
I beg you
我求求你
do you think an ordinary man
你认为一个普通人
would forgive something like this?
会原谅这样的事情吗？
Am I an ordinary guy?
我是一个普通人吗？
I don't know
我不知道
you have to fight for it
你必须为之奋斗
chance to be forgiven.
有机会被原谅。
Still sick?
仍然不舒服？
It's been blown much better.
已经吹得好多了
You really are.
你真的是。
You're not afraid that Zhao An will cause trouble to you?
你就不怕赵安给你添麻烦？
Why am I afraid of him?
我为什么怕他？
Not like you.
不像你。
Weren't you afraid of problems before?
以前就不怕出问题吗？
But you can't just kill people either.
但你也不能随便杀人。
I realized something
我意识到一些事情
since we got married,
自从我们结婚以来，
i...
我...
Full of justice.
充满正义感。
Do you think this is the power of love?
你认为这就是爱的力量吗？
I even feel it
我什至感觉到了
since we got married
自从我们结婚以来
you're getting better at talking
你越来越会说话了
but
但
Feng Qi's
Feng Qi's
was the most ruthless person under Zhao An.
是赵安手下最狠的人。
And the most ambitious under Zhao An.
而赵安手下最有野心。
In the future, don't look for problems with him.
以后别再找他的麻烦了。
Oh yes
哦是的
What did you do at the store today?
今天你在商店做了什么？
What new tasks do you have?
你有什么新任务？
Secret assignment.
秘密任务。
But it doesn't matter if I tell you.
但我告诉你也没关系。
Who told you to be my wife, right?
谁让你做我妻子的，对吧？
In the Chongqing area,
在重庆地区，
was holding secret peace talks with the Japanese government.
正在与日本政府进行秘密和谈。
Peace talks?
和平会谈？
War will stop.
战争将会停止。
How could it be?
怎么会这样？
Both parties sent representatives
双方均派出代表
to do this exchange of intentions in Shanghai.
这次在上海做意向交流。
However, the Japanese military strongly opposed it.
但遭到了日本军方的强烈反对。
And make representations of both sides
并提出双方交涉
as an assassination target.
作为暗杀目标。
Village Chief Mu gave this mission to Zhao An,
穆村长把这个任务交给了赵安，
but if Lao Luo wants to seize merit,
但如果老罗想要夺功，
so he told me to look into it.
所以他告诉我要调查一下。
Time and place of this meeting
本次会议时间、地点
I've really investigated.
我确实调查过。
Where?
在哪里？
In a villa on Jalan Yapet.
Jalan Yapet 的一栋别墅内。
I actually want to make a little spice
我其实想做一点香料
to fight Lao Luo.
去打老罗。
It was unexpected that Zhao An had already left.
没想到赵安已经走了。
He brought a group of people to surround the entire villa.
他带着一群人，将整个别墅围了起来。
So
所以
negotiator has been arrested.
谈判代表已被捕。
I've arrested two people.
我已经逮捕了两个人。
The others had run away.
其他人已经逃跑了。
So what about the two people who were arrested
那么被捕的两个人呢？
Then, how?
那么，如何呢？
After that, definitely...
在那之后，肯定...
Why are you so interested in this?
你为什么对此如此感兴趣？
I'm worried about you.
我很担心你。
Worried about me?
担心我吗？
Okay
好的
then I will explain to you
然后我会向你解释
how am I not afraid to face danger
我怎么不害怕面对危险
always meet at a dead end
总是在死胡同里相遇
Chen Ping's family
陈平一家
his body was light like a swallow
他的身体轻如燕子
jump over the wall.
跳过墙。
Jumping
跳跃
immediately jumped into the villa
立刻跳进了别墅
but Commander Luo once told me,
但罗司令曾经告诉我，
can't let Zhao An
不能让赵安
also know we interfered in this,
也知道我们干涉了这件事，
So, I can't let Zhao An find me.
所以，我不能让赵安找到我。
The situation at that time
当时的情况
really very urgent.
真的非常紧急。
Zhao An, get the front door of the villa
赵安，到别墅门口去
and the back door
和后门
already besieged.
已经被围攻了。
I was confined to the second floor
我被限制在二楼
really can't be free anymore.
真的不能再自由了。
Apparently today I saw a person who
显然今天我看到一个人
inside the villa
别墅内
is Chen Jia Ping
是陈家平
Then?
然后？
Then,
然后，
take a nap and then talk to you.
睡个午觉然后再跟你说话。
No way, you haven't finished talking yet.
不可能吧，你还没说完呢。
You really want to know?
你真的想知道吗？
You can too.
你也可以。
But today I am
但今天我是
step on the wall and back and forth.
踩在墙上来回走动。
You see.
你看。
My feet are swollen.
我的脚肿了。
Can you soak your feet?
可以泡脚吗？
Maybe I can still tell you about it
也许我还能告诉你这件事
Want me to wash your feet
要我给你洗脚
What do you think?
你怎么认为？
I'm just kidding
我只是在开玩笑
How does it feel?
感觉如何？
Can it be powerful?
能强大吗？
Are you going to say no?
你要说不吗？
Let me talk, talk
让我说话，说话
at this time,
此时，
a series of footsteps came from the corridor.
一连串的脚步声从走廊里传来。
I thought, Zhao An had already come.
我想，赵安已经来了。
What should I do?
我应该怎么办？
I can't jump off a building.
我不能从建筑物上跳下去。
I jump.
我跳。
If you don't fall to death.
如果不摔死的话。
Or disabled due to a fall.
或因跌倒而致残。
So, in times of life and death
所以，在生死存亡的时刻
at this critical moment,
在这个关键时刻，
I will show my hero nature.
我会展现我的英雄本色。
I made a firm decision,
我做了一个坚定的决定
jump
跳
what do you think?
你怎么认为？
Sleep downstairs.
睡楼下吧
I mean is
我的意思是
after Zhao An caught the two people,
赵安抓住两人之后，
My wife, don't panic.
我的妻子，别惊慌。
Shouldn't I remember it from the start?
难道我不应该从一开始就记住吗？
Say it.
说吧。
However, it was not Zhao An who came.
然而，来的却不是赵安。
Rupanya Chongqing mewakili Jiang Zhaoguo.
Rupanya Chongqing mewakili Jiang Zhaoguo.
I added water for you.
我给你加了水。
It doesn't matter.
没关系。
Continue.
继续。
Good.
好的。
This Jiang Zhaoguo is also quite strange
这个蒋兆国也挺奇怪的
just like playing tricks
就像玩把戏一样
out of nowhere a grenade was taken out,
不知从什么地方取出了一枚手榴弹，
after the sound of the explosion,
爆炸声响起后，
The atmosphere in the villa became silent
别墅里的气氛变得安静了
I immediately got out from under the mattress
我立即从床垫下爬出来
ran to the window and looked out.
跑到窗边往外看。
A car
一辆车
The person driving the car was a nurse
开车的人是一名护士
nun
尼姑
Have you ever seen a nun driving?
你见过修女开车吗？
I've never seen it either.
我也从没见过。
Just look at this nun
看看这个尼姑
left hand holding a gun,
左手拿着枪，
right hand holding a grenade.
右手拿着一枚手榴弹。
Then how can he drive?
那他怎么开车呢？
This is not important
这并不重要
only saw the nun raise the gun
只看见修女举起了枪
Plaque plaque several times.
匾额数次。
It was Zhao An who was rambling.
胡言乱语的正是赵安。
Then he opened the car door.
然后他打开了车门。
Directly pulled Jiang Zhaoguo into the car.
直接拉着蒋兆国上了车。
To be honest,
说实话，
at that time I was suspicious
当时我很怀疑
is this nurse a man in disguise?
这个护士是男扮女装吗？
where is there a woman as strong as that.
哪里有这么坚强的女人。
Zhao An tak bereaksi,
Zhao An tak bereaksi,
they went by car.
他们开车去的。
Really come and go without a trace.
真是来无影去无踪。
Then?
然后？
Then,
然后，
Want to know what will happen.
想知道会发生什么。
Listen to the next description.
请听接下来的描述。
Good.
好的。
Husband, are you tired?
老公，你累吗？
I'm not tired.
我不累。
Don't wash it again.
别再洗了
Let me soak.
让我泡一下。
I'll help you massage.
我帮你按摩。
Continue.
继续。
Help me massage.
帮我按摩一下。
I still get this treatment.
我仍然接受这种治疗。
You continue.
你继续。
What about those two people Zhao An caught?
赵安抓到的那两个人呢？
Zhao An.
Zhao An.
Those two people.
那两个人。
Then just take it away.
然后就把它拿走。
In that case...
在这种情况下...
Locked up in the shop,
被锁在店里，
must be given a severe punishment, right?
应该受到严厉的惩罚吧？
I didn't hear Zhao An bringing people back to the shop,
没听到赵安带人回店里，
probably hidden somewhere.
可能隐藏在某个地方。
What place?
什么地方？
So who knows
那么谁知道呢
not true.
不对。
Left twin.
左边双胞胎。
Why do you pay more attention to these two people
为什么大家更关注这两个人
more attentive than me?
比我还细心？
What's that?
那是什么？
I'm not paying attention.
我没注意。
But curiosity is strong.
但好奇心却很强烈。
So, when you hear a book assessment, you have to hear the end of the story, right?
所以，当你听到书评时，你必须听到故事的结局，对吗？
Good.
好的。
I'll just find out later.
我稍后会知道。
Once I know I will let you know.
一旦我知道了，我就会告诉你。
Good.
好的。
It turns out he really wanted to provoke me to talk.
原来他是真的想挑衅我说话。
If I didn't guess wrong,
如果我没猜错的话
guoguo definitely wanted to save the two captured people.
果果肯定是想救那两个被抓的人。
This girl is really looking for death.
这丫头真是找死啊。
Greetings to Mrs. Luo
问候罗女士
where are you going?
你要去哪里？
Kapten Zhao.
Kapten Zhao.
I'm out taking care of something
我出去处理一些事情
just right
正好
give me a lift.
载我一程。
Where are you going?
你要去哪里？
Where will I go.
我要去哪里。
Today
今天
What is it?
它是什么？
Enough already.
已经足够。
Can no longer.
不能再了。
I miss you.
我想你。
Hey.
嘿。
Mr. Chen, this is Han Lu.
陈先生，这是韩露。
This is last month's financial report.
这是上个月的财务报告。
The manager has already signed it.
经理已经签字了。
OK, then I'll go to the Finance Bureau.
好的，那我去财政局。
Nona,
诺娜，
I'll give you a bunch of lilies.
我送你一束百合花。
Welcome to the golden rose flower shop
欢迎来到金玫瑰花店
which we just opened.
我们刚刚打开的。
I don't like lilies.
我不喜欢百合。
You'll love it
你一定会喜欢的
besides, you will often come here to buy flowers.
另外，你会经常来这里买花。
I thought you guys went to Chongqing.
我还以为你们去了重庆呢
You saved Jiang Zhaoguo.
You saved Jiang Zhaoguo.
Do you still want to continue blaming me for disobeying your orders?
你还想继续指责我不听你的命令吗？
You misunderstood.
你误会了。
Previously I rejected this action,
之前我拒绝了这个动作，
because I don't feel sure I can finish it.
因为我不确定我能完成它。
However, you exceeded my expectations.
然而，你超出了我的预期。
However, Zhao An still arrested two people.
不过，赵安还是逮捕了两人。
So, our mission is not finished.
所以，我们的使命还没有完成。
Already become
已经成为
our mission again.
我们的使命又来了。
Correct.
正确的。
You have to get ready
你必须做好准备
long-term lurking in Taihe Business Industry.
长期潜伏在太和商业。
Director Guan Yongshan of the 2nd Military Commander Division
军长第二师师长关永山
Have agreed to this proposal.
已同意此提议。
Can last a long time
可以持续很长时间
Isn't this according to your wishes?
这不是按照你的意愿吗？
That's right, right?
没错，对吧？
You look at these two photos.
你看看这两张照片。
Can you tell which one is fake?
你能看出哪个是假的吗？
Recently in Chongqing appeared
近日在重庆出现
large amounts of counterfeit French money like this.
大量像这样的法国假币。
to my knowledge
据我所知
French watermark technology provided by the UK
英国提供的法国水印技术
very difficult to fake
很难造假
and mostly French money
大部分是法国钱
printed by the Americans for us.
美国人给我们印的。
Their printing technology is the greatest in the world,
他们的印刷技术是世界上最伟大的，
Japanese troops
日军
has spent almost two years researching
花了近两年的时间研究
also did not find
也没有找到
can counterfeit French money
可以伪造法国钱
So how do you get these French coins?
那么如何获得这些法国硬币呢？
German submarine
德国潜艇
in the Pacific Ocean destroying American warships
在太平洋摧毁美国军舰
and confiscated much unfinished French money.
并没收了许多未完成的法国资金。
They sold this to the Japanese government
他们把这个卖给了日本政府
to research the Japanese people.
研究日本人。
Provides great convenience
提供了极大的便利
so our mission is
所以我们的使命是
investigate
调查
and destroy this fake money plan.
并摧毁这个假钱计划。
Development of counterfeit money
假币的发展
is a big and professional project
是一个大而专业的项目
However, now we don't have any clues.
然而，现在我们没有任何线索。
However, the Taihe Company where you operate...
然而，你们经营的太和公司……
Because it was directly under the command of the Japanese gendarmerie,
因为是日本宪兵队直属指挥，
moreover, economically, he and the Japanese army
而且，在经济上，他和日军
economically.
经济上。
It will definitely be key in our research
这绝对是我们研究的关键
I can take your orders
我可以接受你的命令
but I have one condition.
但我有一个条件。
What conditions?
什么条件？
You are not allowed to touch Chen Jia Ping again
不准再碰陈家平
he is now your best protection
他现在是你最好的保护
I won't touch it.
我不会碰它。
Don't know Miss Han Lu,
不知道韩露小姐，
What kind of fan association do you want to form?
你想成立什么样的粉丝协会？
If you can be like you who are willing to sacrifice and die for celebrities,
如果你能像你一样愿意为明星牺牲、牺牲，
Is Mr. Jiang safe?
江先生安全吗？
Are you the one who helped him?
你是帮助他的人吗？
I only helped a little.
我只帮忙了一点点。
There were other people who saved Mr. Jiang.
还有其他人救了江先生。
Do you know?
你知道吗？
You could say you know.
你可以说你知道。
Also not familiar.
也并不熟悉。
I understand.
我明白。
But don't understand.
但不明白。
Master Jiang just left.
江大师刚刚离开。
Didn't leave anything for you.
没有给你留下任何东西。
Just think of it as leaving a promise.
只是把它想象成留下一个承诺。
So what
所以呢
Miss Han Lu didn't go with Master Jiang?
韩露小姐没跟江老爷子一起去？
This question must be asked of you men.
这个问题必须问你们男人。
I think Mr. Jiang
我觉得蒋先生
has its own difficulties
有其自身的困难
dan Du Chun, penerjemah Jiang Zhaoguo
dan Du Chun, penerjemah Jiang Zhaoguo
must be saved
必须保存
before he worked for us,
在他为我们工作之前，
he had been a translator
他曾是一名翻译
in military lessons in Nippon Province.
在日本省上军事课。
And who led the research and printing of this fake money
谁领导了这种假币的研究和印刷
is this military lesson.
这就是军事课。
Those caught were two people.
被抓的人是两个人。
The other is looking at his luck.
另一个就看他的运气了。
You really haven't changed a bit.
你确实一点都没变。
Do you know where Zhao An locked up people?
你知道赵安把人关在哪里吗？
I just knew he definitely wasn't in the shop.
我只知道他肯定不在店里。
Isn't Chen Jia Ping in charge of general affairs?
陈家平不是主管总务吗？
He has a lot of business.
他有很多生意。
You look to him for guidance.
你向他寻求指导。
Why?
为什么？
I couldn't bear to pull him into the water.
我不忍心把他拉到水里。
I'll think of a way.
我会想办法。
Good.
好的。
And also your files.
还有你的文件。
I've sent it to the main headquarters of the General Bureau.
我已经发到总局总部了。
Think of a name for yourself.
为自己想一个名字。
Head Guan,
关主任，
and also Boss Dai.
还有戴老板。
They must know your movements at any time.
他们必须随时知道你的动向。
His name is Hong Tao Wu.
他的名字叫吴洪涛。
Why?
为什么？
I heard inside a commercial bank
我听说商业银行里面
there was a CCP spy codenamed Meihua Si.
有一个中共特务，代号梅花斯。
I, the red heart 5,
我，红心5，
happens to be greater than him.
恰好比他大。
Plum blossom four.
梅花四朵。
5 hearts.
5 颗心。
Just look at this card.
看看这张卡就知道了。
Who will win in the end?
最终谁会获胜呢？
I still haven't decided
我还没决定
is it necessary to wear the ring he gave me.
他送我的戒指有必要戴吗？
It turned out to be the promise that Mr. Jiang left behind
原来是江先生留下的承诺
is a ring.
是一个戒指。
I'd like to ask
我想问一下
is this ring a diamond ring?
这枚戒指是钻戒吗？
Owned by Han Lu.
属于韩露。
Don't get me wrong.
别误会我的意思。
Like this,
像这样，
when I married Shuang Tao,
当我和双涛结婚的时候
have renovated, bought furniture,
装修过，买过家具，
order a banquet, buy a wedding dress,
订酒席、买婚纱、
My savings are basically gone.
我的积蓄基本没了。
So when buying a ring,
所以买戒指的时候
don't buy diamonds for the left twin peaches.
不要为左双桃买钻石。
So, he always blames me.
所以，他总是责怪我。
So I also want to see
所以我也想看看
stuff that makes women dream
让女人梦想的东西
what kind of thing?
什么样的事情？
I actually brought it.
我确实带来了。
This box
这个盒子
looks better than mine.
看起来比我的好。
This... Such a big diamond ring?
这……这么大的钻戒？
How much does it cost?
它要多少钱？
This is two carats
这是两克拉
if it's French money
如果是法国钱
almost 1,000 Yuan more.
又多了将近1000元。
1,000 Yuan more.
多了1000元。
I'd better tell him
我最好告诉他
dreaming of two more years
梦想再过两年
actually,
实际上，
this diamond is smaller.
这颗钻石较小。
Or no diamonds,
或者没有钻石，
no problem
没问题
What matters is the intention.
重要的是意图。
Women will not forget it for the rest of their lives.
女人一辈子都不会忘记。
So true.
如此真实。
For Han Lu,
对于韩璐来说，
will Mr. Jiang call again?
江先生还会再打电话来吗？
He said he would call me again.
他说他会再给我打电话。
If you like,
如果你喜欢，
I want to ask Mr. Jiang for help
我想请姜先生帮忙
fainted again
再次晕倒
remove water
除去水
Enough already.
已经足够。
Ketua Zhao,
Ketua Zhao,
just leave it.
别管它吧。
These two people really don't know
这两个人确实不认识
keberadaan Jiang Zhaoguo.
keberadaan Jiang Zhaoguo.
If it continues like this,
如果再这样下去的话
we will lose our lives.
我们会失去生命。
I heard that Village Chief Mu will be back tomorrow.
听说穆村长明天就回来了。
If not,
如果不，
immediately hand over these two people to the Military Police Headquarters.
立即将这两人移交给宪兵司令部。
Tell them to go interrogation.
叫他们去审讯。
What the two knives said made sense
两把刀说的有道理
Mosquitoes are also meat.
蚊子也是肉。
At least we can give assignments,
至少我们可以布置作业，
why did Village Chief Mu hand over
穆村长为何交出
this to us?
这对我们来说？
Is for
是为了
commander of the Military Police Soldiers
宪兵司令
clearing the relationship with this issue.
理清与此问题的关系。
Actually, Jiang Zhaoguo and these two negotiators
其实蒋兆国和这两个谈判者
had guessed the truth behind this attack
猜到了这次袭击背后的真相
but they have no proof
但他们没有证据
if we tell these two people
如果我们告诉这两个人
operation this time
这次的操作
is the main envoy of the Military Commander.
是军事统帅的主要使者。
Those who do.
那些这样做的人。
Then release them.
然后释放他们。
Let them spread the information everywhere
让他们到处传播信息
what the results will be
结果会是什么
leader
领导者
what you mean is...
你的意思是...
Using these two people to threaten Village Chief Mu?
用这两个人来威胁穆村长？
We don't have to live anymore.
我们不必再活了。
Doesn't want to live
不想活了
too severe.
太严厉了。
Now these two people
现在这两个人
is our chance to save lives.
这是我们拯救生命的机会。
If that's the case, will we continue to lock them both up?
如果是这样的话，我们还要继续关他们俩吗？
locked up here?
被锁在这里？
Not only must it be closed,
不仅必须关闭，
but it must also be guarded strictly
但也必须严密看守
if they both run away
如果他们都逃跑了
we are completely devastated.
我们彻底崩溃了。
Good.
好的。
Mari
马里
what do you think?
你怎么认为？
I seem to know Zhao An,
我好像认识赵安，
where he hid it.
他把它藏在哪里。
Hide where?
藏在哪里？
Hotel Hongyun.
Hotel Hongyun.
How did you know?
你怎么知道？
I told you.
我告诉你了。
I go first.
我先走了。
Don't
不
You have to tell me the truth.
你必须告诉我真相。
I won't do anything to you either.
我也不会对你做什么。
So...
所以...
He took me there.
他带我去了那里。
This is where you two secretly dated first.
这是你们两个第一次秘密约会的地方。
Allow?
允许？
Before.
前。
Before?
前？
Say.
说。
What?
什么？
He used to take me to Junyue hotel.
他曾经带我去君悦酒店。
This time he took me away.
这次他带我走了。
Then?
然后？
Then,
然后，
then I realised,
然后我意识到，
he was very close to the owner of the Hongyun hotel.
他和鸿运宾馆的老板关系很密切。
Very familiar.
很熟悉。
Very familiar with what?
很熟悉什么？
What else is there?
那里还有什么？
After I left,
我离开后，
he still lives there.
他仍然住在那里。
It seems that there is something very important
似乎有一件很重要的事情
I have told you everything.
我已经告诉你一切了。
What do you still want me to do?
你还想让我做什么？
Zhao An.
Zhao An.
Penginapan Hongyun.
Penginapan Hongyun.
Mrs. Luo,
罗女士，
who are you waiting for?
你在等谁？
Shocking.
令人震惊。
Didn't you say you'd go home from work together?
你不是说要一起下班回家吗？
Where are you going?
你要去哪里？
I,
我，
out to take care of something.
出去照顾某事。
Go away.
离开。
Go home.
回家。
What is it?
它是什么？
Me.
我。
Pergi mengikuti Da Ma Shao.
Pergi mengikuti Da Ma Shao.
What for with him?
跟他有什么关系？
He always reports fake accounts,
他总是举报虚假账户，
he said he was running errands
他说他正在办事
but actually he takes people for a walk,
但实际上他带人去散步，
eventually even produced a lot of messy production.
最终甚至产生了很多乱七八糟的生产。
My boss blamed me for not being firm in my assessment.
我的老板责备我的评估不够坚定。
Today he quietly went out again.
今天他又悄悄出去了。
I just want to catch him
我只想抓住他
the result
结果
forwarding comments we haven't finished yet
转发评论我们还没有完成
that we haven't finished yesterday.
我们昨天还没有完成。
There's something new.
有新东西了。
Then you hurry.
那你就快点吧。
Tell me, let me hear.
告诉我，让我听听。
At that time
当时
Zhao An didn't arrest two people,
赵安没有抓两个人，
not caught back to this shop?
没抓回这家店？
However, I don't know where it is hidden anymore.
然而，我已经不知道它藏在哪里了。
Try to guess.
猜猜看。
Where have he and I been?
我和他去哪儿了？
Where to?
去哪儿？
Hotel Hongyun.
Hotel Hongyun.
Penginapan Hongyun?
Penginapan Hongyun?
After I thought about it,...
我想了想之后，...
Why did this Horse Spoon go to Hongyun Hotel?
这个马勺怎么会去鸿运宾馆？
I...
我...
My wife.
我的妻子。
I happen to be hungry.
我正好饿了。
How about we talk while eating?
我们边吃边聊怎么样？
Good.
好的。
Ate.
吃。
Mr Boss.
老板先生。
Two oil cutting boards
两块油菜板
two eggs.
两个鸡蛋。
Good.
好的。
Fast.
快速地。
Here.
这里。
Good.
好的。
Continue.
继续。
Why does Zhao An want to go to Hongyun hotel?
赵安为什么要去鸿运酒店？
I'm looking for a hidden corner.
我正在寻找一个隐蔽的角落。
We will see later.
我们稍后会看到。
I want to investigate what he did.
我想调查他做了什么。
In the end, he did not enter.
最终他没有进去。
Even find some
甚至找一些
several friends who helped him work outside.
几个帮助他在外面工作的朋友。
After I thought about it,
我想了想之后，
da Ma Shi invited other people to stay at the hotel,
大马士邀请其他人入住酒店，
I'll pay later.
我稍后付款。
I immediately made a decision,
我当即做了一个决定，
I've also joined in.
我也加入了。
The result
结果
Guess who I met inside?
你猜我在里面遇见了谁？
Who?
WHO？
I met Zhao An's subordinates!
我见到了赵安的手下！
What two stabs?
什么两刺？
Chen Shu Gan
Chen Shu Gan
everything inside.
里面的一切。
But...
但...
Husband.
丈夫。
Large horse spoon.
大马勺。
Why are you hanging out with Zhao An's subordinates?
你怎么和赵安的手下混在一起？
You misunderstood.
你误会了。
The big horse spoon is Commander Luo's subordinate.
大马勺是罗司令的部下。
Dan bawahan Zhao An,
Dan bawahan Zhao An,
is the enemy.
是敌人。
Jadi, Da Ma Shao
Jadi, Da Ma Shao
not with them anymore.
不再和他们在一起了。
It was arranged by Commander Luo.
这是罗司令安排的。
What did Luo send him for?
洛派他来干什么？
Tuan.
团。
Pour egg oil
倒入蛋油
you eat slowly
你吃得很慢
Thank You.
谢谢。
Commander Luo arranged for him.
罗司令给他安排了。
Of course it won't work.
当然行不通。
Try to think about it,
试着想一想，
Zhao An arrested the two people,
赵安将两人抓了起来，
not just not reporting,
不仅仅是不报告，
even kept secret.
甚至保密。
If these two people escape,
如果这两个人逃走的话
and was known by Village Head Mu.
并被穆村长认识了。
Try to think about it,
试着想一想，
how is Zhao An's fate?
赵安的命运如何？
But if I have great power
但如果我有强大的力量
and arrested the two people again
并再次逮捕了两人
then I will reverse the situation.
那我就扭转局势。
Are you selling this fragrance bag?
你们卖这个香包吗？
Looks like I'm the one selling it.
看来是我卖的
This woman,
这个女人，
have you ever seen it?
你见过吗？
I do not remember.
我不记得了。
You think carefully,
你仔细想想，
was he the one who bought this fragrance bag here?
这个香包是他在这里买的吗？
Correct.
正确的。
It did come.
它确实来了。
Since when did he buy fragrance pouches?
他什么时候开始买香包了？
A month ago,
一个月前，
more specific,
更具体，
let me think about it.
让我想想。
That's how it should be.
事情应该是这样的。
Oh yes
哦是的
April 16th lunar calendar.
农历4月16日。
I entered that day on the 15th of the fourth month,
我进入那一天是四月十五日，
to the train station to sell it.
到火车站去卖。
He was the first person to come and buy it.
他是第一个来买的人。
So I remember clearly,
所以我记得很清楚，
16th day of the fourth month of the lunar calendar.
农历四月十六日。
Emperor's Calendar?
皇帝的历法？
Do you want it or not?
你想要还是不想要？
Always.
总是。
Five corners?
五个角？
Not.
不是。
One Yuan.
一元。
April 16th lunar calendar.
农历4月16日。
16th day of the fourth month of the lunar calendar
农历四月十六
on May 22 of the Gregorian calendar,
公历5月22日，
the day Da Xiao from the mountains came to Shanghai
大山里的大晓来到上海的那天
I ask you,
我问你，
when this woman bought a fragrance pouch,
当这位女士买了香包时，
about what time?
大约什么时间？
The time is very early.
时间还很早。
About seven o'clock less.
大约七点多了。
The Wuyi train that Da Zo rode under the mountain
大佐在山下乘坐的武夷列车
that's right, leaving at 7:45.
没错，7点45分出发。
Very good.
非常好。
All are correct.
全部正确。
Don't accept it anymore.
别再接受了
Why?
为什么？
You want to run away?
你想逃跑吗？
I will not return this money.
我不会退还这笔钱。
I ask you,
我问你，
how much does this fragrance pouch cost?
这个香水袋多少钱？
Eight?
八？
Not.
不是。
Three hundred meters?
三百米？
I gave 50 times the price
我给了50倍的价格
but you have to come with me somewhere
但你必须跟我去某个地方
say again what you said earlier
再说一遍你刚才说的话
go where?
去哪里？
Shanghai.
上海。
Very far.
非常远。
So what about my business?
那么我的生意呢？
I guarantee you will arrive in ShangHai
我保证你一定会到达上海
good food, good drinks, interesting place,
美味的食物，美味的饮料，有趣的地方，
a hundredfold?
一百倍？
100 times the money I'll go.
100倍的钱我就去。
Good.
好的。
Only 100 times.
只有100次。
I'm used to bad luck
我已经习惯了霉运
now I don't know
现在我不知道
how could it be my turn?
怎么轮到我了？
You have no proof,
你没有证据，
I have to write a guarantee letter for me.
我得给我写一份保证书。
Why are you so bothered?
你为什么这么烦恼？
If you don't write, I don't go.
你不写我就不去。
Good.
好的。
Write.
写。
Let me write it.
让我写一下。
You wrote it.
你写的。
Oh yeah, what's your name?
哦，是的，你叫什么名字？
Feng Qi
Feng Qi
You wrote me Feng Qi promised that Li Youtian
你写信给我 冯琪答应李有天
namaku Li Youtian.
namaku Li Youtian.
Say.
说。
Make sure that after Li Youtian arrives in Shanghai,
确保李友田到达上海后，
can be safe
可以安全
and also,
并且，
say down.
说下来。
Why the rush?
为什么这么着急？
I rarely go to Shanghai,
很少去上海，
cannot bring gifts for wife and children.
不能给妻子和孩子带礼物。
You write again.
你再写吧。
I guarantee that I will help Li Youtian
我保证一定会帮助李有田
bought a three-yellow chicken from Hong Xiang Ji.
向红香记买了一只三黄鸡。
Hung Xiang.
Hung Xiang.
Still have.
还有。
Fuyun Zhai red bean paste cake.
Fuyun Zhai red bean paste cake.
Apart from that, it must be guaranteed
除此之外，还必须保证
reimburse all travel expenses
报销所有差旅费
also the cost of eating at a restaurant
还有在餐馆吃饭的费用
Is it finished writing?
写完了吗？
You've pushed me.
你推了我。
Enough already.
已经足够。
As soon as you press me,
只要你一按我，
I wrote it wrong at the hotel.
我在酒店写错了。
Don't be afraid of writing mistakes.
不要害怕写错。
The meaning is correct.
意思是正确的。
This.
这。
Give me two more dollars.
再给我两块钱。
What? Two Yuan?
什么？两块钱？
These banknotes and brushes,
这些钞票和刷子，
for you.
为你。
Good.
好的。
Why look at me?
为什么看着我？
Exciting.
令人兴奋。
Look at you.
看着你。
Where are you going?
你要去哪里？
Throw in the cucumber
把黄瓜扔进去
Why? Why are you so nervous?
为什么？你为什么这么紧张？
Go to sleep.
去睡觉。
You sleep first.
你先睡吧。
I want to read a book for a while.
我想看一会儿书。
You also go to bed early.
你也早点睡觉。
I still have to work tomorrow.
明天我还要工作。
Good night.
晚安。
Tonight
今晚
their people
他们的人
will definitely go to Hong Yun hotel to help people
一定会去鸿运酒店帮忙的人
look at him like this
像这样看着他
doesn't look like he's going to take part in the action.
看起来他不会参加这个行动。
But it can't be confirmed.
但无法证实。
The important thing is that I couldn't sleep all night.
重要的是我整晚都睡不着。
Have to keep an eye on him.
必须留意他。
Guoguo.
Guoguo.
What's wrong with you?
你这人怎么回事？